## **LUKE CULBERTSON**

Portfolio: www.lukeculbertson.com E: wlculbertson@gmail.com

P: 360.241.0931

#### WHO I AM:

I'm a multi-disciplinary creator with over 5 years of experience in visual design, creative direction and marketing design, seeking a new opportunity to further develop my skills. I enjoy working outside traditional boundaries and techniques to create unique and captivating imagery.

# PROGRAMS/SKILLS:

- Mac/Linux/Windows OS
- HTML/CSS
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Microsoft Office Suite
- G Suite
- Figma
- Ableton Live 10
- Davinci Resolve

- Customer Service
- Communication
- Collaboration
- Research
- Time Management

## **EXPERIENCE:**

November 2021 - Present

Seattle, WA

#### WILL CALL ASSOCIATE

Working as a seasonal will call associate at evo, shipping packages and interacting with customers retrieving online orders. Using HighJump and Oracle's NetSuite for inventory management and order processing.

February 2020 - Present Freelance Seattle, WA/Remote

#### **GRAPHIC DESIGNER/AUDIO PRODUCER**

Working as a freelance graphic designer and music producer/mixing engineer for a variety of freelance clients.

April 2018 - February 2020

Filter/REI Seattle, WA

# **PRODUCTION DESIGNER**

Worked as a production designer for a brand new team providing consulting and design work for REI's email marketing program. Designed email creative for all marketing channels at REI, developed template systems, created training documentation, and trained new designers.

April 2017 - November 2017 HackerAgency Seattle, WA

## JR. ART DIRECTOR

Worked as a jr. art director with HackerAgency directly supporting the AT&T acquisition team, designing direct mail marketing materials and concepts, as well as animated GIF web ads and supporting email campaigns.

April 2016 - March 2017

Amazon Seattle, WA

**VISUAL DESIGNER** Worked on the newly-formed D1 Creative team to support Private Label branding projects, creating mockups & layouts, sourcing imagery, developing multiple brands' images and styles with business partners, and shadowing photoshoots. Also created cross-site marketing graphics for various business teams and trained new employees.

January 2015 - December 2015

**VISUAL DESIGNER** 

Amazon Seattle, WA

Worked as a visual designer on Amazon's ACS design team, creating web ads, postcards, and specialized projects, balancing heavy workloads and tight deadlines. Trained new employees in basic Amazon design practices. Worked closely with art directors on logo projects and brand design.

#### **EDUCATION:**

Seattle Pacific University

**BACHELOR OF ARTS DEGREE**